Finding Aid for the Ralph Story Papers LSC.0867
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 1. Broadcasting -- Radio and Television
  - Television, Specials, 1966 - 1996
    - KCET "Things That Aren't Here Anymore" -- viewer comments and letters, press clippings, 1995 and later (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - KCET "More Things That Aren't Here Anymore" -- research and correspondence, 1995 - 1996 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - KCET "More Things That Aren't Here Anymore" -- research, 1995 - 1996 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - KCET "More Things That Aren't Here Anymore" -- scripts, drafts, 1995 - 1996 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - "Then 2 Now" -- script and photo, CBS special on occasion of the station changing its call letters from KNXT to KCBS, 1984 April 2 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - KNXT/CBS -- "The Very Last Resort", 1966 (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - Palm Springs film, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - KNXT/CBS -- Judy Garland special, 27 November 1978 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - KNXT/CBS -- Lucille Ball special, undated (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Storyline Corporation -- "Journey to Los Angeles" -- notebook -- organization, ca. 1979 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Storyline Corporation -- "Journey to Los Angeles" -- notebook -- contacts, ca. 1979 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Storyline Corporation -- "Journey to Los Angeles" -- notebook -- bibliography, ca. 1979 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Storyline Corporation -- "Journey to Los Angeles" -- notebook -- audio visual, ca. 1979 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Storyline Corporation -- "Journey to Los Angeles" -- notebook -- resources copies, ca. 1979 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Proposal -- "Porciuncula", 1980 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - "Then to Now" -- CBS call letter change, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - 80th Tournament of Roses -- souvenir program, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - 88th Tournament of Roses -- commentator's notebook, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - 89th Tournament of Roses -- souvenir program, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - 89th Tournament of Roses -- commentator's notebook, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - 90th Tournament of Roses -- souvenir program, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - 92nd Tournament of Roses -- judges notebook, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Pilot ideas for television specials, undated (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Script for Nick Walker, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 17)
- 2. Print Projects
  Typescript drafts, research, staff records.
  - An Introduction to Los Angeles, 1984
    Chapter for "Official Olympic Guide to Los Angeles."
    - Correspondence, draft, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Guide book "Ralph Story's Los Angeles", bulk 1968 - 1971
    Drafts, research, contracts: Unpublished guidebook along lines of television series "Ralph Story's Los Angeles." Assistant Stephanie Edwards Bach. Chapters arranged by neighborhood or theme. Research files contain promotional materials, menus, clippings, drafts.
    - General -- proposal, outlines, notes (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Publication Contracts, drafts, none executed (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Researchers -- administrative records, contacts and assignments, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Introduction -- drafts (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Downtown -- drafts, story ideas (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - San Fernando valley -- draft one, story ideas (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - San Fernando valley -- final (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - San Fernando valley -- follow up (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Wilshire -- final (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Hollywood -- final (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Hollywood -- draft one and story ideas (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Beverly Hills -- final (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Beverly Hills -- draft one and story ideas (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Sunset Strip (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Santa Monica -- final (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Santa Monica and the Beaches -- draft and story ideas (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Long Beach -- final and draft one (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Valley San Gabriel -- final and draft one (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Art -- final and draft one (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Churches / Religion -- drafts and story ideas (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Calendar -- drafts and story ideas (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Architecture -- story ideas (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - East Los Angeles -- draft one and follow up (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Bunker Hill -- research (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Central City -- research (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - San Fernando valley -- research (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - San Fernando valley -- research (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Glendale and Burbank-- research (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Hollywood -- research (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Hollywood -- research (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Hollywood -- research (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Calendar chapter -- research (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Valley San Gabriel -- research (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Valley San Gabriel -- research (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Research guidelines and assorted notes (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Century City -- research (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Where are they now? -- draft (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Introduction -- research (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Santa Monica -- research (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Santa Monica -- research (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Santa Monica -- research (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Long Beach and harbor -- research (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Beverly Hills -- research (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Wilshire -- research (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Valley San Gabriel -- research (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Downtown -- research (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Downtown -- research (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Long Beach and harbor -- research (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Long Beach and harbor -- research (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Wilshire -- research (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Wilshire -- research (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Wilshire -- research (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Wilshire -- UCLA -- research (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Way out West -- Indians in Los Angeles -- research (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Wilshire -- research (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - San Fernando Valley -- research (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Hollywood -- research (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Orange -- research (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Valley San Gabriel -- research (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Beverly Hills -- research (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Santa Monica and Topanga -- research (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Valley San Gabriel -- follow up research (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Santa Monica -- follow up research (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - LA Mart -- research (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - American Theater Arts -- research (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles cultural Heritage Board -- research (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Catalina and Channel islands -- research (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Cars -- research (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Gardens -- research (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Sports -- research (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Inglewood -- follow up research (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - How To Be A Tourist -- draft (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - The Big Eight -- brochures for Disneyland, Knott's, Hollywood Wax Museum, Universal Studios tour (also MGM and 20th Century Fox, Farmer's Market, Marineland, Japanese Village and Deer Park (not represented: Network TV tapings and tours of stars' homes) (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Religion -- research (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Art -- research (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Art -- research (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Architecture -- research (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Food -- research (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Calendar -- research (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Calendar -- research (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous -- research (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous -- research (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence -- book and story ideas (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Assorted menus and business cards (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Assorted publications (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Westways magazine -- 4 issues, 1969 March, 1971 November,1971 December, 1972 January (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Assorted oversized menus (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Assorted oversized publications (Box 58, Folder 2)
      Pictorial California and the Pacific, December 1968; color Xerox of Harper's Bazaar cover, October 1962; Los Angeles Times special supplement on the Los Angeles County Art Museum, March 28, 1965; Los Angeles Times special supplement on city bicentennial, august 31, 1980; 2 issues of Bien, Danish language newspaper, May 13, 1976 and April 14 1982
    - Assorted urban and suburban development brochures (Box 58, Folder 4)
      Centropolis, plans for downtown development 1964; Calabasas Park, undated; California Federal Building, undated
    - Oversized Xeroxes of news clippings, poster promoting "It's a Nice Place?," (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Downtown -- drafts (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Wilshire corridor -- drafts (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Hollywood and San Gabriel Valley -- drafts (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Sunset and the Strip -- drafts (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Beverly Hills -- drafts on cards (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Beverly Hills -- drafts (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Mixed research and drafts (folder 1 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Mixed research and drafts (folder 2 of2) (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - General research (folder 1 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - General research (folder 2 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Rancheros -- research for portion of book (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Introduction -- draft -- early version (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Introduction -- draft -- edited version (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Introduction -- draft -- marked up (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Introduction -- draft --edited after mark up (Box 65, Folder 6)
- 3. Personal Appearances
  Speeches and lectures, hosting gigs, commercials, cameos, stage roles.
  - First annual Ralph Story tennis tournament, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - First annual Ralph Story tennis nostalgia trip, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Don Juan in Hell-- program, press, telegrams; Lady I Saw You With-- press clipping; Academy of Television Arts and Sciences panel-- program, thank you letter, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - City of Los Angeles speech, includes notes, correspondence, 1973 October 31 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Junior Achievement lecture, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Braille institute -- class appearance, includes notes, correspondence, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Airport fill -- Barney Miller promo, includes scripts, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Gas company commercial, includes storyboards, notes, correspondence, 1975 July 16 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Hollywood Bowl -- July 4th concert-- script, 1976 July 4 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Hollywood Bowl -- July 4th concert -- research, 1976 July 4 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Hollywood Bowl -- Peter and the Wolf, 1972 July 24 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Smokenders, includes script, certificate, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - The Long Escape -- cameo appearance, includes agreement, script, 1977 January 1 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Titanic anniversary, includes script, invitation, press, 1977 April (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Pierce College Ecology Lecture, includes notes, schedule, correspondence, 1977 April 18 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - "Step right up!" -- voiceover for industrial film produced by Film Communicators, includes script, agreement, 1977 July (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Pasadena City College -- Ralph Story Service Award, includes correspondence, program, 1977 June and 1978 May (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Glendale Federal -- Commercials and Senior Olympics, includes scripts, storyboards, production records, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Second Half lecture, includes notes, photo, undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Winners and losers -- script for filmstrip, correspondence, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - San Bernardino Orange Show, includes speech notes, correspondence, schedule, 1978 March 30 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - San Bernardino Citrus festival, includes background research, bulk 1977 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Citrus research, bulk 1977 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles County -- USC Medical Center centennial celebration, includes notes, correspondence, certificate of appreciation, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Ole L.A. speech -- financial executives conference, includes notes, correspondence, event brochures, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - 2 undated scripts -- "Working with the media" and "Understanding the media" (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Radio control plane -- P-51, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Bazaar del Mundo -- script for radio, correspondence, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - San Bernardino County Medical Society -- notes, background, schedule, 1979 April 3 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - San Luis Obispo -- community promotional materials, 1979 - 1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - 92nd Tournament of Roses Parade -- programs, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - California gift show -- speech notes, ca. 1980 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Pacific Design Center appearance -- background research, correspondence, notes, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Solvang -- scripts, background research, undated (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Cuesta College -- speeches, short courses, 1985 - 1986 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Lompoc Flower festival, 1985 - 1988 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Voiceover scripts Burger King, Sanyo, Union 76, undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Senior magazine article -- correspondence, article, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Freeway 2000 script, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Douglas S. Cramer Foundation, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Ernest Goes to Splash Mountain -- script for cameo appearance, 1989 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Glenn Miller salute, 1990 August 4 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Installation of star for Ruth Ashton Taylor on Hollywood Walk of Fame -- invitation, script, 1990 December 13 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Air strike training -- script, 1991 February 12 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Alice in Wonderland, 1994 May (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Pacific Pioneer Broadcasters -- Diamond Circle awards, 1990 -2005 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Assorted speeches -- note cards, clippings, drafts, correspondence, 1980 - 1994 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Background research for speech on Buddy Baker, after 1985 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Assorted speeches, appearances -- notes, correspondence, 1952 - 2002 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Tennis tournaments -- programs, schedules, 1970s (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - The Lucy Show -- script, 1968 January 9 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - The Lucy Show -- photo of Story with Lucille Ball and Ken Berry, undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - The Doris Day show -- call sheet and script, 1972 July (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - 2 issues of Society West, 1977 July and August (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Santa Maria Museum of Flight, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Douglas S. Cramer Foundation -- art tours, 1994-1997 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Douglas S. Cramer Foundation -- tours to ranch and galleries, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Various appearances and lectures 1985 - 1990 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Various appearances and lectures 1991 - 1996 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - UCLA Film and Television Archives, 1990 - 1992 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Maggie Awards -- presenter, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- 4. Professional Career/History
  Contracts, resumes, correspondence, publicity, awards, uncategorized research.
  - Awards
    - Awards and honors, certificates, 1956 - 2006 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      Including Los Angeles Area Emmy nominations, California Associated Press certificates, and City of Los Angeles Tribute
    - Los Angeles Area Emmy statue for "More Things That Aren't Here Anymore", 1996 (Box 60)
    - Radio and TV News Association of Southern California Award for Best Documentary for "On the Road Again", 1982 (Box 61)
    - Academy Television Awards, 18 April 1970 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Award certificates, 1980 - 1970 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Awards speeches, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
      Examples of others' speeches.
  - Contracts
    - Contracts, 1949 - 1968 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Contracts, 1956 - 1980 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Contracts, 1962 - 1985 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Contracts and agent correspondence concerning contracts, 1949 - 1960 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Contract correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Contracts -- Abrams-Rubaloff and Associates, 1970 - 1976 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Contracts, 1976 - 1986 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - American Federation of Television and Radio Actors -- permits, 1968 - 1969 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Car reimbursement reports, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1959 and later
    Business correspondence, fan mail, kudos. Letters include thank yous, story ideas, invitations and responses to research requests. For some programs, additional correspondence can be found under the program's title in series 1. Broadcasting -- Radio and Television, above.
    - Resumes -- potential hires, not Story's resume (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Photocopies of letters from notable people-- Hubert H. Humphrey, Sue Vidor, Winter D. Horton, Lucille Ball, Ed Reineke, Lawrence Welk, Tom Bradley, Mary Astor (original in box 30 folder 6); original correspondence from Leon Drew, and one illegible (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Letters -- from colleagues, viewers (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Letter from Jeremy Roos of the Los Angeles Jewish Community Council, 1951 April 4 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Letters -- from colleagues, viewers, includes letter with photos from 1902-1903, including Pasadena Flower Festival; invitation and thank you from Mayor Tom Bradley, 1972 - 1993 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Letters -- kudos and compliments, 1959 -1984 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Letters -- fan mail, 1983 - 1985 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Letters -- fan mail, includes snapshots sent by viewer of Story on television screen, 1982 - 1984 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Various correspondence, 1950 - 1951 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      Includes two original drawings by the cartoonist Al Johns which he sent to Story.
    - Correspondence -- military, 1951 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Various correspondence, 1951 - 1985 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Various correspondence, 1951 - 1992 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Various correspondence, 1951 - 1977 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Guest book embossed with "Ralph Story's Backyard", 1953 - 1954 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Various correspondence, 1964 - 2000 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Fan mail -- Hearst Castle special (KNXT), 1967 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Responses to burglary of Story's home, 1974 - 1976 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Fan mail -- AM America, ca. 1974 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Kudos, 1976 - 1980 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Various correspondence, 1976 - 2000 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Terse Verse, 1977 - 1982 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - CBS memorandums, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous newsletters, 1981 - 2000 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Fan mail, 1983 - 2004 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - KNXT news, 1980 - 1984 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Tenure recommendation letters, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Various correspondence, 1994 - 2006 (Box 66, Folder 16)
      One letter from 1966 included.
    - Pacific Pioneer Broadcasters -- newsletters and professional correspondence, 1995 - 1999 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Fan mail -- "The Things that Aren't Here Anymore", 1996 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - KCET -- phone messages, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Stanely Martin letters and photographs, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Invitations and tickets, 1996 - 1997 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - CBS Alumni Newsletters, ca. 1996 - 2000 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Poems, 1998 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      Includes poems that do not appear to be authored by Story (many of which are about him) but rather sent to him in some manner, but there are no letters accompanying the poems.
    - Pacific Pioneer Broadcasters -- correspondence and newsletters, 1998 - 2001 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - 43-K Contact Aviation Cadet Newsletter, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Pacific Pioneer Broadcasters -- Jack McQueen, 1999 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Suzanne Vidor Parry, undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
      Includes a draft memoir.
    - Lists of local press members, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Publicity and press
    Includes press releases, biographies, clippings, and appearances in publications.
    - Media research -- clippings, teletypes, trade publications, notes, bulk early 1980s (Box 47, Folder 7)
      Emphasis on television journalism, CBS and KNXT, but also national trends and developments such as 24 hour cable news
    - Biographies, 1950s - 2006 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      Station press releases, newspaper clippings, obituaries
    - Tributes, memorials, 2006 - 2007 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      Written by colleagues, friends and family including: Dan Gingold; Sylvan C. "Ace" Diamond; Bradley Johnson Snyder
    - Name change documents, photocopy, 1967 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Clippings and press releases, 1950 and later (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Clippings, 1951 and later (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Clippings -- includes report on home robbery 1976 and CBS publicity, 1948 and later (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1948 - 1980 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1950s (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1952 - 1988 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Press packet -- KNX "The Story Showcase", 1953 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Publicity -- personal, 1953 - 1984 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      The contents of this folder are clippings and press releases concerning Story as a local figure in Los Angeles and New York, not directly in conjunction with a specific television or radio show.
    - CPRN -- five year presentation to Bank of America, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1956 - 1993 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Press releases, 1957 - 1993 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Theater-related clippings, 1958 - 1962 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Clippings -- Story's stage performances, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - KNX radio publicity, 1961 - 1962 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Clippings and press releases, 1961 - 1984 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Press releases, 1962 - 1980 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Clippings from the Hollywood Reporter, 1963 - 1975 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - KNXT/CBS publicity and clippings, 1965 - 1972 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, ca. 1965 - 1975 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1966 - 1970 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, 1966 - 1978 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1966 - 1984 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1966 - 1992 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, ca. 1968 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, 1969 - 1982 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - KABC Eyewitness news -- press releases and clippings, 1971 - 1972 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Ralph Story's AM America -- clippings, 1971 - 1972 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - KNBS Sunday Show -- clippings, 1975 -1976 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Press releases, 1975 - 1980 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Stephanie Edwards -- clippings, 1975 - 1999 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Home burglary -- clippings, ca. 1974 - 1976 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Clippings, 1982 - 1985 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - KCBS Wine Game -- photocopies of clippings and publicity, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Los Olivos -- clippings, late 1980s (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous undated clippings (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Radio at War, ca. 1944 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      Story pictured on page 19 (pages unnumbered).
    - WGR 1922 Till Now: more than 25 years of service, ca. 1947 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      Story pictured page 13.
    - TV Life (1 - 7 December 1956), 1956 December 1-7 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      Includes the article: Bruce, Jon. "Ralph Story: Confessions of an Emcee." TV Life (1-7 December 1956): 4-5.
    - TV Life (1 - 7 December 1956), 1956 December 1-7 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      Identical to the object in previous file.
    - TV Radio Mirror (December 1956), 1956 December (Box 70, Folder 5)
      Includes the article: Anderson, Lila. "Faith in His Fellow Man." TV Radio Mirror (December 1956): 44-45,63.
    - Nadler, Teddy. Secrets of My Million Dollar Memory. New York: Jetsam Publishing, 1957. (Box 70, Folder 6)
      Terry Nadler was a contestant on the "$64,000 Challenge," and Ralph Story is mentioned and pictured within the magazine-style publication.
    - Western Michigan University News Magazine, vol. 15, no. 2, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 7)